module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Who is the most decorated athlete in Olympics history?', 
      a: 'Larisa Latynina',
      b: 'Michael Phelps',
      c: 'Nickolai Andrianov',
      d: 'Boris Shakhlin',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'How tall is the tallest tree in the world?', 
      a: '379.7 ft',
      b: '321.2 ft',
      c: '298.1 ft',
      d: '275.0 ft',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is Angela Merkel\'s middle name?', 
      a: 'Anne',
      b: 'Bertha',
      c: 'Meekel',
      d: 'Dorthea',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What are protons made of?', 
      a: 'Quarks',
      b: 'Hadrons',
      c: 'Gluons',
      d: ':shit:',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many seasons did Michael Jordan play in the NBA?', 
      a: '11',
      b: '15',
      c: '12',
      d: '16',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'In what year was the Theramin patented?', 
      a: '1901',
      b: '1912',
      c: '1922',
      d: '1928',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who made this emoji: :aloh-awk: ?', 
      a: ':chelsb-emoji-queen:',
      b: ':call-center-brendan:',
      c: ':haley-dealwithit:',
      d: ':good-bill:',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the world\'s first web browser named?', 
      a: 'Netscape aka Netscape Navigator',
      b: 'WorldWideWeb aka Nexus',
      c: 'AOL aka America Online',
      d: 'Internet Explorer aka Hot Garbage',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What movie won the Oscar for Best Picture in 1982?', 
      a: 'Chariots of Fire',
      b: 'E.T.',
      c: 'Raiders of the Lost Ark',
      d: 'On Golden Pond',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many hearts does a squid have?', 
      a: '1',
      b: '2',
      c: '3',
      d: '8',
      answer: 'c'
    }
  ]
};